eqads.com 2015-06-11

# Online Privacy Policy | EQ Works

You are here: [Home](http://www.eqworks.com/ "EQworks") / Privacy Policy

EQ Ads is committed to earning your trust and confidence. To better protect privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online technology and information collection practices.

### EQ Ads’ Technology Platform

EQ Ads has created a demand-side technology platform that our clients use to purchase advertising inventory from multiple sources through real-time bidding. EQ Ads’ platform allows our clients to target and connect with web consumers based on their online searches and behaviour.

### Collection and Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information

The EQ Ads platform only collects non-personally identifiable information. We collect this information through mechanisms such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, pixel tags, search history, and number of clicks. The information is used to analyze trends, administer the EQ Ads platform, track users’ movements in the aggregate, optimize advertising delivery, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in relation to the EQ Ads platform. We use this non-personally identifiable information to display targeted and optimized advertisements that we believe may be relevant to your interests. In seeking to identify relevant advertisements, we use this information to develop and refine algorithms and to understand how your interaction with a website might be of interest to advertisers. This information and data is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

EQ Ads’ platform may also employ cookies to help customize and track the advertisements that may be displayed when you browse the web. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website’s computer and stored on your computer’s hard drive. These cookies do not provide EQ Ads with any personally identifiable information about a web user. They are used to facilitate targeting of certain advertisements to web users.

### Third Party Data and Cookies

EQ Ads may obtain data from third party companies for the purpose of informing ad selection. This data is supplied in aggregate form and does not include any personally identifiable information.

### Opt-Out

Consumers have the ability to opt out of EQ Ads targeted advertising, cookies and tracking at any time by utilizing our opt out mechanism. Please [click here ](http://eqworks.com/optout) to submit a request to opt out of our targeted advertising For a period of five years, opting out will completely remove all advertisements served by EQ Ads platform from your web browsing experience and display untargeted advertisements in any ad space you encounter that is delivered by EQ Ads platform. Users who choose to opt out must have cookies enabled on their Internet browsers.

### Data Retention

Unique user identification numbers, associated with when and how many times an individual has seen an advertisement, are created and deleted after 90 days of user inactivity. These unique IDs are not tied to any personally identifiable information. Aggregated statistical information, such as the popularity of an advertiser campaign, will be retained as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Online Behavioural Advertising

EQ Ads prides itself on providing an atmosphere that is non-disruptive to web users. Our proprietary targeting and optimization methodologies enable advertisers to effectively target their advertising campaigns to the consumers they are looking to reach without engaging in profiling practices.

### Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information by Advertisers

Advertisers who are clients of EQ Ads may collect personally identifiable information on their own websites. These details provided directly by an individual web user in the form of online order forms, contests, or otherwise through the advertiser’s website, are not visible to EQ Ads. This personally identifiable information collected by the advertiser is subject to the privacy policy of the individual advertiser involved. As a result, we disclaim any and all responsibility for, or affiliation with, any third party cookies, pixels or practices.

### Security

We employ reasonable industry standard measures to protect against the unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or destruction of the non-personally identifiable information we collect. While we are committed to ensuring the security of such information, you should be aware that no information protection measures can provide 100% guarantee of security. Consequently, we do not warrant or guarantee the security of the non-personally identifiable information

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

EQ Ads may find it necessary to update this privacy policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted at this site. Except as otherwise required by law, any modifications made to this privacy policy will not materially affect the privacy of data collected by EQ Ads prior to the effective date of the policy change. By visiting the website of any of our clients or partners, you hereby consent to our collection, storage, and dissemination of the non-personally identifiable information as described above.

### Effective Date and Governing Law

This policy was updated on May 2, 2012. This privacy policy and any matter relating to the EQ Ads platform shall be governed by the laws of Canada. If any part of this agreement is deemed to be invalid, illegal or unenforceable, then the invalid or unenforceable part shall be removed without affecting the legality, validity and enforceability of the remainder of this privacy policy.

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, you can reach us through our online form at [http://eqworks.com/contact/](http://eqads.com/contact/) or [privacy@eqads.com](mailto:privacy@eqads.com), or at the following address:  
EQ Ads  
1255 Bay Street  
Suite 400  
Toronto, On  
M5R 2A9  
Tel: 416-260-4493  
Fax: 416-597-2345

Scroll to top
